HE was more than a cop. SHE was more than a thief.
No Good Deed is a action, crime, drama film directed by Bob Rafelson.
While doing a friend a favor and searching for a runaway teenager, a police detective
stumbles upon a bizarre band of criminals about to pull off a bank robbery.
Jack Friar, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Erin, played by Milla Jovovich.
Tyrone, played by Stellan Skarsgård.
Hoop, played by Doug Hutchison.
Mr. Quarre, played by Joss Ackland.
Mrs. Quarre, played by Grace Zabriskie.
No Good Deed is a 2002 American crime thriller film
directed by Bob Rafelson, his last feature film.
It stars Samuel L.
Jackson, Milla Jovovich, Stellan Skarsgård and Doug Hutchison.
The screenplay by Christopher Cannan and Steve Barancik is based on the
short story "The House in Turk Street" by Dashiell Hammett.
The original music score is by Jeff Beal.
It was entered into the 24th Moscow International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of robbery, police, hostage, bank, detective.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.